https://luma-metall.com/general-website-privacy/

HomeFine Wire ProductsPRODUCT OVERVIEWProduct RangeProduct overviewProperty ComparisonProduction ProcessFINE WIRE PRODUCTSTungsten WireTungsten-Rhenium WireMolybdenum WireGold Plated Tungsten WireGold Plated Silver WireGold Plated Molybdenum WireGold Plated Beryllium Copper WireGold Plated Brass WireGold Plated Copper WireGold Plated Stainless Steel WireGold Plated Tungsten-Rhenium WirePlatingQuality AnalysisStandard AnalysisCase Studies and ReportsTechnologySpoolsDownloadsAbout usHistoryNewsOur teamReferencesSustainabilityContact usYour enquiry
General Website Privacy
You can use the Luma-Metall AB Group website universe without disclosing your identity. Details of the information that we gather as standard when you access the websites is described below. If you register for any of our services or contact us via forms, there will be detailed information about how your data is processed in connection to your registration.
Identity and contact details of the controller and data protection officerAB Luma-Metall AB (“Luma-Metall AB”), as controller of personal data, is responsible for the processing of personal data that relate to you under applicable data protection laws and regulations.
If you have questions regarding the processing of your personal data, please contact Luma-Metall AB’s data protection officer at DPO_Office@Luma-Metall AB.com or by post or phone at:
AB Luma-Metall AB, Att: Data Protection Office, Dept AA14100, VLH, SE-405 08 Göteborg, Sweden
+46 (0)31 66 00 00What categories of personal data will Luma-Metall AB process, for which purpose and based on what legal basis?
When you access any Luma-Metall AB website, your web browser is technically configured to automatically transmit the following data (“log data”) to our web server, which we then capture in log files:• Date of access
• Time of access
• URL of the referring website
• File retrieved
• Data volume transmitted
• Browser type and version
• Operating system
• IP address
• Domain name of your internet access providerThis is exclusively information which does not allow you to be identified. This information is necessary for technical purposes in order to correctly deliver the content requested by you and its collection is an unavoidable aspect of using websites. The log data is analyzed purely for statistical purposes in order to improve our website and its underlying functionality. Luma-Metall AB will process your personal data based on the legal basis legitimate interest. Luma-Metall AB’s legitimate interests include the interest to manage its websites according to fair business practices and to maintain availability and functionality of the websites.Cookies
We use cookies and tracking pixels to gather data regarding your use of the website in order to tailor the website to its users’ needs. The gathering of this usage data and the creation of a usage profile is carried out on an anonymized basis using a cookie ID. We create and store these usage profiles solely in anonymized form and do not combine them with your name or with any other information such as your email address which may reveal your identity.
Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. With the information contained in cookies, we can simplify navigation and facilitate the correct display of our websites.
Each website has its own cookies statement where you as a user can see the exact cookies usage for that specific site.Forwarding of data to third parties
Luma-Metall AB may, if necessary to fulfill the purpose for processing the personal data, or if required by law or regulation share your personal data with other Luma-Metall AB Group company, including company outside of the European Union or the European Economic Area EU/EEA. Luma-Metall AB may also, if necessary to fulfill the purpose for processing the personal data, share your personal data with third party companies and suppliers including companies and suppliers outside the EU/EEA.
We work with a range of different service providers to deliver the Luma-Metall AB Group website universe. Luma-Metall AB will secure that appropriate safeguards are in place which provide adequate levels of protection of your personal data as required by applicable data protection laws.Links to other websites
Our websites may contain links to other websites. We have no influence on the compliance or non-compliance of the operators of these sites with the data protection provisions.For how long will Luma-Metall AB keep your personal data?
Luma-Metall AB will keep your personal data as long as required to fulfill the purposes for which the personal data was collected.Your data protection rights
You have the right to request from Luma-Metall AB information about the personal data processed about Luma-Metall AB and access to such personal data. You also have a right to request rectification of your personal data if this is incorrect and request erasure of your personal data. Further, you have a right to request restriction of the processing of your personal data meaning that you request Luma-Metall AB to limit its processing of your personal data under certain circumstances. There is also a right for you to object to the processing based on legitimate interest or processing for direct marketing. You have as well the right to data portability (transfer of your personal data to another controller) if Luma-Metall AB’s processing if your personal data is based on consent or contractual obligation and is automated.You also have the right to lodge any complaints you may have regarding Luma-Metall AB’s processing of your personal data to a supervisory authority.Copyright © Luma Metall AB 2018Powered by: Aditor ABThe Internet pages of the Luma-Metall AB use cookies. Cookies are text files that are stored in a computer system via an Internet browser.
Privacy Preferences
I Agree
HomeFine Wire ProductsPRODUCT OVERVIEWProduct RangeProduct overviewProperty ComparisonProduction ProcessFINE WIRE PRODUCTSTungsten WireTungsten-Rhenium WireMolybdenum WireGold Plated Tungsten WireGold Plated Silver WireGold Plated Molybdenum WireGold Plated Beryllium Copper WireGold Plated Brass WireGold Plated Copper WireGold Plated Stainless Steel WireGold Plated Tungsten-Rhenium WirePlatingQuality AnalysisStandard AnalysisCase Studies and ReportsTechnologySpoolsDownloadsAbout usHistoryNewsOur teamReferencesSustainabilityContact usYour enquiry
